thedailyinquirer.net 2012-11-23

# Privacy Policy - The Daily Inquirer

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you accept the practices described here.

**Collection of Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors.

**E-mail Subscription**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to my posts via e-mail _(powered by Feedburner)_ , I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for my users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
Our site may use cookies and tracking technology which are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.   

Third parties such as our advertisers may also use cookies to serve ads to you based on your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. If you want to opt out of our third-party advertiser (Google Adsense)’s use of cookies, please visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

**Infolinks Clause**  
These links are part of a [pay per click advertising](http://www.infolinks.com/Home.html) program called Infolinks. Infolinks is an In Text advertising service; they take my text and create links within it. If you hover your mouse over these double underlined links, you will see a small dialog box containing an advertisement related to the text. You can choose to move the mouse away and go on with your browsing, or to click on the box and visit the relevant ad. [Click here to learn more about Infolinks Double Underline Link Ads.](http://www.infolinks.com/opt-out.html?pid=20561&wsid=1)
